[
    {
        "question": "What was the Minecraft 1.13 update called?",
        "quiz1": "Update Aquatic",
        "quiz2": "The Aqua Update",
        "quiz3": "The ocean update",
        "correct": "Update Aquatic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What other country, besides the US, uses the __US__ dollar as its official currency?",
        "quiz1": "Ecuador",
        "quiz2": "Mexico",
        "quiz3": "Canada",
        "correct": "Ecuador"
    },
    {
        "question": "What measurement scale is used to determine wind speed?",
        "quiz1": "Beaufort scale",
        "quiz2": "Richter scale",
        "quiz3": "Discord Canary",
        "correct": "Synoptic scale"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the biggest country?",
        "quiz1": "United States",
        "quiz2": "China",
        "quiz3": "Russia",
        "correct": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many continents are there?",
        "quiz1": "6",
        "quiz2": "7",
        "quiz3": "8",
        "correct": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the russian capital?",
        "quiz1": "Moscow",
        "quiz2": "St. Petersburg",
        "quiz3": "Omsk",
        "correct": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the US capital?",
        "quiz1": "Los Angeles",
        "quiz2": "Washington D.C.",
        "quiz3": "Las Vegas",
        "correct": "Washington D.C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the japanese capital?",
        "quiz1": "Kyoto",
        "quiz2": "Tokyo",
        "quiz3": "Sendai",
        "correct": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the south-african capital?",
        "quiz1": "Johannesburg",
        "quiz2": "Bloemfontein and Pretoria",
        "quiz3": "Cape town, Bloemfontein and Pretoria",
        "correct": "Cape town, Bloemfontein and Pretoria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did discord create Discord Nitro?",
        "quiz1": "2016",
        "quiz2": "2017",
        "quiz3": "2018",
        "correct": "2016"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift to the United States from which European country?",
        "quiz1": "Belgium",
        "quiz2": "Germany",
        "quiz3": "France",
        "correct": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the biggest discord bot?",
        "quiz1": "MEE6",
        "quiz2": "Dyno",
        "quiz3": "Rythm",
        "correct": "MEE6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most common discord bot language?",
        "quiz1": "Discord.py",
        "quiz2": "Java Discord API",
        "quiz3": "Discord.js",
        "correct": "Discord.js"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which continent are Chile, Argentina and Brazil?",
        "quiz1": "North America",
        "quiz2": "South America",
        "quiz3": "Europe",
        "correct": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": "The human body is made up of approximately how much water?",
        "quiz1": "50%",
        "quiz2": "60%",
        "quiz3": "70%",
        "correct": "60%"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is actually electricity?",
        "quiz1": "A flow of protons",
        "quiz2": "A flow of air",
        "quiz3": "A flow of electrons",
        "correct": "A flow of electrons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wich of the following is not a US agency?",
        "quiz1": "FBI",
        "quiz2": "National Science Foundation",
        "quiz3": "DDA",
        "correct": "DDA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following disorders is the fear of being alone?",
        "quiz1": "Agoraphobia",
        "quiz2": "Aerophobia",
        "quiz3": "Acrophobia",
        "correct": "Agoraphobia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name for the Jewish New Year?",
        "quiz1": "Hanukkah",
        "quiz2": "Yom Kippur",
        "quiz3": "Rosh Hashanah",
        "correct": "Rosh Hashanah"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?",
        "quiz1": "6",
        "quiz2": "9",
        "quiz3": "13",
        "correct": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet is the hottest?",
        "quiz1": "Venus",
        "quiz2": "Saturn",
        "quiz3": "Mercury",
        "correct": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the only U.S. President to resign?",
        "quiz1": "Richard Nixon",
        "quiz2": "Herbert Hoover",
        "quiz3": "George W. Bush",
        "correct": "Richard Nixon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the “D” in “D-Day” stand for?",
        "quiz1": "Dooms",
        "quiz2": "Dark",
        "quiz3": "Day",
        "correct": "Day"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was Captain Jack Sparrow’s ship’s name?",
        "quiz1": "The black pearl",
        "quiz2": "The blue earl",
        "quiz3": "The Boat",
        "correct": "The black pearl"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the rarest blood type?",
        "quiz1": "AB Positive",
        "quiz2": "AB Negative",
        "quiz3": "A",
        "correct": "AB Negative"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state is known as the sunflower state?",
        "quiz1": "Kansas",
        "quiz2": "Florida",
        "quiz3": "The Boat",
        "correct": "Kansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
        "quiz1": "193",
        "quiz2": "206",
        "quiz3": "234",
        "correct": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following options is NOT a country?",
        "quiz1": "Vatican City",
        "quiz2": "Kiribati",
        "quiz3": "Amsterdam",
        "correct": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What time-zone is MDT?",
        "quiz1": "-3", 
        "quiz2": "+2",
        "quiz3": "-6",
        "correct": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "How long is the longest paved runway in the world?",
        "quiz1": "4573 meter (15003 ft)", 
        "quiz2": "12000 meter (39370 ft)",
        "quiz3": "5000 (16404 ft)",
        "correct": "5000 (16404 ft)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the biggest desert?",
        "quiz1": "The Sahara desert", 
        "quiz2": "The Arctic desert",
        "quiz3": "The Antarctic desert",
        "correct": "The Antarctic desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the director of the very popular movie 'Titanic'?",
        "quiz1": "James Cameron", 
        "quiz2": "David Yates",
        "quiz3": "Steven Spielberg",
        "correct": "James Cameron"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the folowing youtubers does NOT play on the Hermitcraft Minecraft server?",
        "quiz1": "Mumbo Jumbo", 
        "quiz2": "TommyInnit",
        "quiz3": "Stressmonster101",
        "correct": "TommyInnit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete the sentence: 'A heist with ...'?",
        "quiz1": "Pewdiepie", 
        "quiz2": "Mr Beast",
        "quiz3": "Markiplier",
        "correct": "Markiplier"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Davie504 play?",
        "quiz1": "Double Bass", 
        "quiz2": "Bass",
        "quiz3": "Guitar",
        "correct": "Bass"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does LED stand for?",
        "quiz1": "Light Emitting Diode", 
        "quiz2": "Light Emitting Diamond",
        "quiz3": "Light Emitting Drink",
        "correct": "Light Emitting Diode"
    },
    {
        "question": "Holland is part of which country?",
        "quiz1": "France", 
        "quiz2": "Italy",
        "quiz3": "The Netherlands",
        "correct": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many runways does the airport with most runways have?",
        "quiz1": "6", 
        "quiz2": "8",
        "quiz3": "10",
        "correct": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most sold helicopter in the US?",
        "quiz1": "Robinson R44", 
        "quiz2": "Bell 206",
        "quiz3": "Mil Mi-8",
        "correct": "Mil Mi-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many runways does the airport with most runways have?",
        "quiz1": "6", 
        "quiz2": "8",
        "quiz3": "10",
        "correct": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many inversions does The Smiler at Alton Towers have? (Most inversions on a roller coaster in the world)",
        "quiz1": "11", 
        "quiz2": "12",
        "quiz3": "13",
        "correct": "13"
	},
	{
        "question": "Who said: 'From this day foreword, it will only be America First, America First!'",
        "quiz1": "Barack Obama", 
        "quiz2": "Donald Trump",
        "quiz3": "Joe Biden",
        "correct": "Donald Trump"
	},
	{
        "question": "What is the Guiness World Record for solving a 3x3x3 Rubics Cube?",
        "quiz1": "3,47 seconds", 
        "quiz2": "3,57 seconds",
        "quiz3": "3,67 seconds",
        "correct": "3,47 seconds"
	},
	{
        "question": "How many languages are there in the world?",
        "quiz1": "Over 6500", 
        "quiz2": "Over 7500",
        "quiz3": "Over 8500",
        "correct": "Over 6500"
	},
	{
        "question": "14th of July is the National Celebration Day of what country?",
        "quiz1": "United States of America", 
        "quiz2": "United Kingdom",
        "quiz3": "France",
        "correct": "France"
	},
	{
        "question": "Which of these coding languages is not a programming language?",
        "quiz1": "HTML", 
        "quiz2": "JavaScript",
        "quiz3": "Python",
        "correct": "HTML"
	},
	{
        "question": "How long did it take to land on the moon? (Time between lift-off and landing)",
        "quiz1": "4 days, 6 hours, 35 minutes and 32 seconds.", 
        "quiz2": "4 days, 6 hours, 45 minutes and 32 seconds.",
        "quiz3": "4 days, 6 hours, 45 minutes and 40 seconds.",
        "correct": "4 days, 6 hours, 45 minutes and 40 seconds."
	},
]
